{
    "subject": "resource/Pennsylvania",
    "predicate": "property/fish",
    "object": "resource/Brook_Trout",
    "human_readable": "The fish of Pennsylvania is Brook Trout.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9802801012992859,
            "question": "Is Brook Trout a popular game fish in Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7702353000640869,
            "question": "How does the Brook Trout contribute to Pennsylvania's ecosystem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.747227132320404,
            "question": "Does Pennsylvania have any conservation efforts in place for Brook Trout?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6693075299263,
            "question": "What kind of fish is the state fish of Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6639094352722168,
            "question": "Name the fish that represents Pennsylvania."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6155303716659546,
            "question": "Where is the Brook Trout commonly found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5790750980377197,
            "question": "What is the official state fish of Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5570970177650452,
            "question": "Which fish species is associated with the state of Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5055023431777954,
            "question": "What characteristics make the Brook Trout a suitable state fish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2648683488368988,
            "question": "Are there any other state symbols besides the fish of Pennsylvania?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The fish of Pennsylvania is Brook Trout.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7936_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What characteristics make the Brook Trout a suitable state fish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7936_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which fish species is associated with the state of Pennsylvania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7936_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the official state fish of Pennsylvania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7936_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7936_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms the state fish of Pennsylvania is indeed the Brook Trout. There are multiple mentions of this fact throughout the documents, making it a supported statement based on the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The fish of Pennsylvania is Brook Trout.\" For instance, several documents mention that brook trout is Pennsylvania's state fish."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}